Miscellaneous Art Exhibition Catalog Collection
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Art Exhibition Catalogs: A-C, Series 1:
  - Bourgeois Galleries, 668 Fifth Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - Exhibition of American Sculptures, January 11-February 1 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Exhibition of Nine Landscapes Painters, October 16-November 10 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Drawings by Jennings Tofel, February 8-March 1 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Exhibition of Modern Art, November 11-December 7 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Exhibition of Modern Art, February 10-March 10, 1917 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Annual Exhibition of American Painters & Sculptors, March 26-April 14, 1923 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - [Invitation] Paintings by Arnold Friedman, November 28-December 19, 1925 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Braun Galleries and Maison Ad. Braun et Cie, 13 W. 46th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - Futurist Paintings by Frances Simpson Stevens, March 8 - 27 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Paintings by Emil Holzhauer, November 18-December 2 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Ossip L. Linde, February 14-March 4 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by A. G. Warshawsky, January 8-18, [1917] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Brearley School, 60 E. 61st St., New York City (Box 2)
    - Bessie Handforth Kunz Memorial Art Exhibition, December 3, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Briant Gallery, 32 Rue de Berri, 32 (Box 2)
    - Edward Bruce: Italian and Provincial Landscapes, February 16 - March 4, 1929 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Brooklyn Museum (Box 2)
    - Exhibition of Water Color Paintings by American Artists, November 7-December 18, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - International Exhibition of Paintings Organized by the Carnegie Institute, January 9 - February 19, 1928 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Exhibition: American and Foreign Artists, February 1 - 28, 1935 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Brooklyn Society of Artists (Box 2)
    - Second Annual Exhibition [Pouch Gallery, Brooklyn], 1919 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Third Annual Exhibition [Grant Post, G.A.R., Brooklyn], 1920 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Brown-Robertson Galleries, 415 Madison Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - Fifth Annual Exhibition of the Painter-Gravers of America, May 14-June 4, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Brummer Gallery, 43 E. 57th St. and 27 E. 57th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - Works by Artists of the Modern French School Also Collection of African Negro Sculpture, November 6-December 2, 1922 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Etchings by Anne Goldthwaite, October 24 - November 23, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Steinlen, March 16-April 18, 1931 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - C. W. Kraushaar Art Galleries, 260 5th Ave. and 680 5th Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - Paintings and Pastels by George Luks, January 17-February 6 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Water Colors by George Luks, January 14-February 2, 1918 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Augustus Vincent Tack, February 12-March 2, 1918 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by John Sloan, March 11-30, 1918 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Decorative Panels and Other Paintings by Augustus Vincent Tack, January 27-February 15, 1919 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Drawings by John Sloan, March 3-22, 1919 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Drawings by Forain, April 12-May 1, 1920 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Drawings by Jerome Myers, April 12-May 1, 1920 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings and Water Colors by George Luks [also an invitation], January 12-31, 1922 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Augustus Vincent Tack, February 7-28, 1922 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Guy Pene du Bois, April 4-30, 1922 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Retrospective Exhibition of Paintings by George Luks, January 8-27, 1923 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Decorative Panels by Augustus Vincent Tack, February 5-28, 1923 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - An Illustrated Catalogue of An Important Collection of paintings, by the following celebrated American Artists: George Luks, Gifford Beal, Guy Pene du Bois, Jerome Myers, John Sloan, Eugene Speicher, Arthur B. Davies, Augustus Vincent Tack, Maurice Prendergast, William J. Glackens, Ernest Lawson, Samuel Halpert, also Marbles and Bronzes by Gaston Lachaise, January 15-February 16, 1924 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Exhibition of Plans and Photographs of Work in Landscape Architecture by Charles Downing Lay, March 16-28, 1925 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - [Announcement] Paintings by Paul Burlin, March 20-April 12, 1926 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - [Announcement] Etchings by C.R.W. Nevinson, September 27-October 9, 1926 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - [Announcement] Exhibition of Water Colors, December 6-27, 1926 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Woodcuts and Etchings by D. Galanis, April 18-May 3, 1927 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Etchings by Walter Pach, April 18-30, 1927 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings, Drawings, Lithographs, and Water Colors by Ernest Fiene, November 12-26, 1927 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Exhibition of Water Colors, December 3-24, 1927 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Guy Pene du Bois, December 6-28, 1927 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Water Colors by Walter Pach, March 11 - 28, 1931 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Carroll Galleries, 9 E. 44 St., New York City (Box 2)
    - Maurice B. Prendergast Paintings in Oil and Water Colors, February 15-March 6, 1915 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Third Exhibition of Contemporary French Art, March 8-April 3, 1915 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Chase's Gallery also J. Eastman Chase's Gallery, 7 Hamilton Place, Boston, Mass. (Box 2)
    - Water-Color Drawings by George W. Harvey, beginning December 8, [1885] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Water Colors by S. P. Rolt Triscott, March 9-23, 1887 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Edward W.D. Hamilton, April 29-May 14, 1892 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by John Leslie Breck, January 16-23, 1893 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Pictures and Sketches by Edmund C. Tarbell, closes March 12, 1894 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Portraits by Sarah G. Putnam, January 4-12, 1895 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Civic Club, 18 East 10th Street, New York City (Box 2)
    - Etchings and Drawings by Hatty Wickey, December 1-15 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Civic Club Gallery, 14 W. 12th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - First Annual Exhibition by the Dialis, February 1-14, 1922 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Barth Verschaeren [annotated], March 13-26, 1922 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Annual Exhibition of Paintings by the Members of the Kit-Kat Club, December 9-23, 1923 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Commonwealth Club, Worcester, Mass. (Box 2)
    - Paintings in Water Color by Ross Turner, November 11-15, [1890] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Contemporary Arts, 41 West 54th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - Otto Botto, February 22 - March 6[13], 1937 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Copley Hall, Boston, Mass. (Box 2)
    - Paintings by Margaret Wendell Huntington, January 19-24, 1914 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Copley Society (Box 2)
    - Loan Collection - Oil Paintings, Water Colors, Pastels, & Drawings, Memorial Exhibition of the Works of Mr. J. McNeill Whistler, [annotated], February 1904 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C. (Box 2)
    - Address of President Roosevelt at the Corcoran Art Gallery, December 15, 1908 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - National Exhibition of Art by the Public Works of Art Project, April 24 - May 20, 1934 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Cottier & Co., 3 E. 40th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - Gari Melchers, undated (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Drawings by Walter Greaves, January 11-February 10, 1912 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Currier Gallery of Art, 192 Orange St., Manchester, N.H. (Box 2)
    - Water Colors by Andrew Wyeth, [May 1939?] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
- Art Exhibition Catalogs: D-F, Series 2:
  - Daniel Gallery, 2 W. 47th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - New Mexican Paintings by Paul Burlin, closing March 4 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Drawings of Old New York by Glenn O. Coleman, closing November 28 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by Samuel Halper t, closing April 20 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Water Colors of Gloucester by Hayley Lever, until March 15 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Middleton Manigault, until March 31 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by Middleton Manigault, closing March 23 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Drawings in Water Color by Charles Demuth, closing December 14 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Annual Exhibition of Water Colors, closing May 14 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Leon Kroll, until March 3 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by Ernest Lawson, closing March 15 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by H. Paul Burlin, closing January 16 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by William J. Glackens, closing January 29 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Water Colors of Naval Activities by Thomas H. Benton, U.S.N., closing December 30 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings & Drawings by Man Ray, until January 16 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Drawings and Paintings by Man Ray, until November 23 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by John Noble, closing February 21 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by Hamilton Easter Field, Carvings in Wood by Robert Laurent, closing April 6, [1915] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Middleton Manigault, closing April 11, [1915] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Special Exhibition - American Art of Today, 1916 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by Ernest Lawson, closing February 28, [1916] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings, Watercolors, Embroideries, by Wm & Marguerite Zorach, until November 28, [1916] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by Hamilton Easter Field and Carvings in Wood by Robert Laurent, closing January 30, [1917] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by Hayley Lever, closing March 27, [1917] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by S. Macdonald-Wright, closing March 18, [1918] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings, Water Colors and Embroideries by William and Marguerite Zorach, closing April 2, [1918] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Man Ray: An Exhibition of Selected Drawings and Paintings Accomplished During the Period 1913-1919, November 17-December 1, 1919 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent Paintings by Samuel Halpert, closing November 18, 1919 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Opening Exhibition, 1920-1921, closing November 16, [1920] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Davis Art Galleries also Davis Studio, Gallery of Arthur E. Davis, 6 Elm St., Worcester, Mass. (Box 2)
    - Exhibition of Paintings - Best Work of American Artists at the Davis Studio; Cor Main & Park Sts., May 20-June 17, 1895 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Catalogue of Oil paintings and Water Colors by George H. Smillie, October 30-November 16, 1895 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Abbott Graves, February 6-18, 1899 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Exhibition and Sale of Water Color Drawings of Paris and the Loire, by Ruel C. Tuttle, April 17-29, 1899 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Detroit Art Loan Association (Box 2)
    - Art Loan Exhibition, February 17, 1883 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Detroit Museum of Art (Box 2)
    - Loan Collection of the Paintings of Mr. Robert Hopkin, November 1907 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Doll & Richards, 2 Park St., Boston, Mass. (Box 2)
    - Paintings and Watercolors by Ross Turner, March 12-21 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Drawings, Water Colors, and Paintings by Mr. John La Farge, January 25-February 6, 1890 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Water Color Paintings by Mr. John La Farge, Mr. Childe Hassam, Miss Lucy S. Conant, November 1902 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Adelaide Cole Chase Exhibition of Portraits of Women and Children, November 30-December 13, 1906 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Durand-Ruel Galleries, 12 E. 57th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - Bellows Exhibition [annotated], February 2-14 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Water Colors and Dry Points by Mary Cassatt, April 5-20 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Catalogue of Works by John La Farge, February 25 - March 5, 1895 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Paintings by Claude Monet and Pierre August Renoir, December 11-31, 1915 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Claude Monet, December 9-23, 1916 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Exhibition of a Series of Paintings of the Avenue of the Allies by Childe Hassam, November 15-December 7, 1918 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Educational Alliance Art School, 197 E. Broadway, New York City (Box 2)
    - Memorial Exhibition of Sculpture, Paintings and Drawings by the late Leo Jackinson [held at Anderson Galleries], May 14-28, 1923 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Twelfth Annual Exhibition, May 22-29, 1926 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Ehrich Galleries also the Print Gallery, 707 5th Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - [Invitation] Exhibition of Photographs by Clarence H. White at Mrs. Ehrich's Gallery, February 1-28 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings and Drawings by Max Weber The Print Gallery, under the Direction of the Ehrich Galleries [annotated], February 1-13, 1915 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Lithoqraphs and Woodcuts on View at the Print Gallery, December 27-January 8, 1916 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings & Monotypes by Henry A. Wight, November 17-December 3, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Englewood Bird Club (Box 2)
    - Van Dearing Perrine Exhibition of Small Paintings and Sketches at His Studio Under the Palisades,..., November 21-28 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Federal Art Project (Box 2)
    - [Invitation] Sculpture Exhibition, March 23 - April 16, 1938 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Sculpture Exhibition, March 23 - April 16, 1938 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Federal Art Project Exhibition, October-December, 1938 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Fifth Avenue Art Galleries, 366 5th Avenue, New York City (Box 2)
    - George Innes, undated (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - William Bradford, A.N.A, Executrix Sale, November 30 - December 1, 1892 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Catalogue of Paintings by the Late A.H. Wyant, N.A., February 5 - 6, 1894 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Paintings by the Late George Innes, N.A., February 2, 1895 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Oil Paintings by the Late Wm. L. Picknell, January 19, 1900 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Fine Art Society, 148 New Bond Street, London (Box 2)
    - Illustrated Catalogue of Two Hundred and Eighty Engravings, Etchings, and Photo-Engravings, 1898 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Illustrated Catalogue of Two Hundred and Sixty Engravings, Etchings, and Photo-Engravings, 1895 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Florence Wilde Studio of Illustration, 63 W. 9th, New York City (Box 2)
    - [Invitation] Exhibition of Student's Work, December 1-4 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Folsom Galleries, 396 5th Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - Decorative Panels in Pastel by Carton Moorepark, undated (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings, Dry-Points and Etchings by Elsie Maria Orleman, February 15 - March 1 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings of California by Paul Harvey, April 21-31 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by William Starkweather, November 8-29 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - The American Salon of Humorists, April 17-May 1, 1915 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Special Exhibition of Porto [sic] Rican Landscapes by Thomas Watson Ball, December 1-18, 1915 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - A Collection of the Work of D. Rice, February 18-March 3, 1916 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Nathaniel Cobb, March 18-April 1, 1916 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Recent paintings Du Bois, Henri, Gifford Beal, Jonas Lie, Hassam, Hawthorne, Richard Miller Carrigan, Dearth, Bruce Crane, Olinsky, Ernest Lawson, Arthur B. Davies, Granville Smith, Ossip L. Linde, November 4-20, 1920 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Recent paintings George Bellows, Guy Pene du Bois, Eugene Speicher, March 10-24, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - The Forum, New York City (Box 2)
    - First Municipal Art Exhibition, February 28 - March 31, 1934 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Fraser Gallery (Box 2)
    - Catalogue of Miniature Portraits, Landscapes, and Other Pieces, February and March, 1857 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Frederick Keppel & Co., 4 E. 39th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - The Art & Etchings of John Henry Twachtman by R. J. Wickenden, undated (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Etchings and Drawings by Earl Horter [announcement also included], September 26-October 14, 1916 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Lithographs of Munition Works by Joseph Pennell, with an introduction by H.G. Wells [announcement also included], February 23-March 17, 1917 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - New York in the Graphic Arts, with an introduction by Carl Zigrosser [announcement also included], February 14-March 2, 1918 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Exhibition of Lithographs by George Bellows, November 7-23, 1918 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Etchings by Joseph Pennell of Railroad Activities done during the years 1918-1919 by permission of the United States Railroad Administration and various other subjects, December 10-31, 1919 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Etchings, Lithographs and Drawings by Kerr Eby, with a note by Captain Walter Jack Duncan, April 6-24, 1920 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Original Lithographs by George Bellows [announcement also included], May 5-June 4, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - The Bliss Collection of Etchings by Forain, April 3-28, 1923 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Catalogue of an Exhibition of Lithographs and Drawings by George Bellows, March 24-April 25, 1925 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - French Institute in the U.S. / Museum of French Art, 599 5th Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - Loan Exhibition of Works by Cezanne, Redon, Degas, Rodin, Gauguin, Derain and others, March 16-April 3, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
- Art Exhibition Catalogs: G-I, Series 3:
  - Galerie Zak, Paris, France (Box 2)
    - Exposition de Dessins et Gravures de Louis Lozowick, July 11-25, 1928 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Galeries Georges Petit, 8 Rue de Seze, Paris, France (Box 2)
    - Exposition d'un Groupe de peintres Americains, July 4-30, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Gallerie Alfred Heller, Berlin, Germany (Box 2)
    - Louis Lozowick, August 1-September 1, 1923 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Gallerie Intime - Anne Pinneo, 749 5th Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - Exhibition by a Group of Younger American Painters, April 11-25 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Landscapes by Julie-Mathilde Morrow, March 20-April 4 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Decorative Screens, Paintings, and Stage Designs by John Wenger, February 20-March 3 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by William Starkweather, November 21-December 11, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Galleries of Foster Brothers, 164 Boylston St., Boston (Box 2)
    - Water Colors in Bermuda by C. Scott White, April 18-May 2, [1894] (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Galleries of J.H. Strauss, 275 Fifth Avenue, New York City (Box 2)
    - Exhibition of Paintings by American Artists, April 19-May 3 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Galleries of Mrs. Albert Sterner [Marie Sterner], 22 W. 49th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - Water Colors by Carl Sprinchorn, March 1-14 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Portrait Drawings in Color by Francis W. Delehanty, March 1-15 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Exhibition of Paintings by Samuel Halpert, March 20-April 1 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - An Exhibition of Drawings From the Portfolios of Albert Sterner, March 2-15 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
    - Paintings by Louise Upton Brumback, April 6-22 (Box 2, Reel 4858)
  - Gallery of the Photo-Secession, 291 Fifth Avenue, New York City (Box 2)
    - Caricatures, Absolute, and Relative by Marius De Zayas, April 18-May 20, 1913 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Exhibition of Photographs by Alvin Langdon Coburn, March 11-April 10, 1907 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Gamut Club, 69 W. 46th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - American Paintings, October 1-November 1 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
  - Gibbs Collection (Box 2)
    - The Gibbs Collection, February 24, 1904 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Gill's, Springfield, Mass. (Box 2)
    - Gill's Exhibition of Paintings in Oil by Noted American Artists [at Art Students Club Rooms, Walker Bldg.], December 1-10, [1892] (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Twenty-Seventh Annual Exhibition of American Artists' Pictures Conducted by James D. Gill [at Stadden's Art Galleries], February 11-March 5, 1904 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
  - Gimpel & Wildenstein, 647 5th Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - First Annual Exhibition of the American Painters, Sculptors and Gravers, November 3-22 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by William T. Dannat to be sold for the benefit of "La Fraternite des Artists de Paris", April 3-May 1, 1915 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Memorial Exhibition of Paintings by Henry Golden Dearth, N.A., January 4-30, 1919 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
  - Goodspeed's Book Shop, 7 Ashburton Pl., Boston, Mass. (Box 2)
    - [Invitation] Water Colors and Pastels by Dwight Williams, Teacher of Arthur B. Davies, November 6-18, 1933 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
  - Gorham Galleries, 5th Ave. at 36th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - First Exhibition of the Works of American League of Young Sculptors, November 15-December 1 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Garden and Decorative Sculpture by Prominent American Artists, March 20-April 15, 1916 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Sculpture Exhibition by Prominent American Artists, November 6-25, 1916 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Decorative Sculpture by American Artists, April 9-May 16, 1917 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Sculpture by Janet Scudder, April 22-May 11, 1918 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Carry On! Exhibition of American Sculpture in the Gallery, November 13-30, 1918 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Second Exhibition of the Young Sculptors Society, April 5-24, 1920 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
  - Goupil & Co. of Paris, 303 5th Ave. and 58 W. 35th St., New York City (Box 2)
    - Paintings - Works of George H. Bogert, April 5-May 5, 1894 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Drawings by Hugo Ballin, November l-15, [after 1915] (Box 2, Reel 4859)
  - Grand Central Art Galleries, 15 Vanderbilt Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - Exhibition of John Singer Sargent, February 23-March 22, 1924 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - 33 Moderns, January 28-February 15, 1930 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
    - Paintings by Frank C. Kirk, November 10-25, 1939 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
  - Greenwich House, 27 Barrow Street, New York City (Box 2)
    - Sculpture, Painting, Crafts by Greenwich Village Artists, April 24-May 2, 1922 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
  - Guild of Boston Artists, 162 Newbury St., Boston, Mass. (Box 2)
    - First General Exhibition by the Guild of Boston Artists, November 2-14, 1914 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Edmund C. Tarbell, and Sculpture by Bela Lyon Pratt, November 16-28, 1914 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
    - Portraits by William James, March 20-April 1, 1916 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
  - H. Wunderlich & Co., 220 5th Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - Drawings and Etchings by J. Alden Weir, February 1895 (Box 2, Reel unfilmed)
  - Haas Gallery, 648 Madison Ave., New York City (Box 2)
    - Paintings and Drawings by Max Weber, April 22-May 8, 1909 (Box 2, Reel 4859)
  - Hanna & Noyes, East Grand Circus Park, Detroit, Mich. (Box 3)
    - Catalogue of Paintings by Robert Hopkin, 1892 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Harlow, McDonald & Co., 667 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - A New Series of Lithographs of New York by Adriaan Lubbers, undated (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Original Drawings and Caricatures Chiefly of People Connected With the Stage by William Auerbach-Levy, A.N.A., December 3-24, 1930 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Hart & Watson's, 423 Boylston St., Boston, Mass. (Box 3)
    - Paintings and Monotypes by Lucy S. Conant, February 28-March 12 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Henry Reinhardt & Son, 565 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Sculpture by Massey Rhind, and Paintings by Edmund Greacen, Karl Anderson, G. Glenn Newell, H.F. Waltman, and Guy Wiggins, March 1-13 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Sculpture and Paintings by Mario Korbel and Walter Dean Goldbeck, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - National Association of Portrait Painters - Annual Exhibition, April 21-May 17, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)